Police have reported a man being bitten by a four -foot snake when he lifted his
toilet seat on Sunday morning.
The snake was not poisonous, so the man did not have to go to the hospital, but his
arm was medically treated at the scene.
The police officer interviewed, told news reporters the snake didn't belong to the
man, and it was unclear how it got into the apartment.
The snake was eventually captured by the local animal handlers and taken to an
animal hospital afterward.
It was being treated for an outer skin infection.
It was unclear who the owner was.
The snake may be taken to a local zoo for care, if the owner does not come forward.
It was being treated for an outer skin infection.
It was unclear who the owner was.
The snake may be taken to a local zoo for care, if the owner does not come forward.
It was being treated for an outer skin infection.
It was unclear who the owner was.
The snake may be taken to a local zoo for care, if the owner does not come forward.
Over the years, other creatures like frogs and fish have found their way into
toilets, but this was the first instance of a snake in recent years.